bankwithsterling.com 2014-02-15

# Sterling Bank | Privacy and Security | Privacy Policy

Sign On to Online Banking

## Privacy Policy

Click here for a print-friendly version (PDF) for your records.

### FACTS

| 

### What does Sterling Savings Bank do with your personal information?  
  
---|---  
  
**Why?**

| Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:  
\- Social Security number and income  
\- Account balances and payment history  
\- Credit history and credit scores  
When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Sterling Savings Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
### Reasons we can share your personal information

| 

### Does Sterling Savings Bank share?

| 

### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purpose -** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| Yes | No  
  
**For our marketing purposes -** to offer our products and services to you

| Yes | No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| Yes | 

No  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your transactions and experiences

| No |  We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday  business purposes -** information about your creditworthiness

| No |  We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

No

|  We don't share  
**For non-affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**Questions?** | Call toll-free 800-650-7141 or visit [**www.bankwithsterling.com**](https://www.bankwithsterling.com/)  
  
Who we are  
---  
  
### Who is providing this notice?

| Sterling Savings Bank and its affiliates. For more information, see Sterling Savings Bank and its Affiliates below.  
  
What we do  
---  
  
### How does Sterling Savings Bank protect my personal information?

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. We restrict access to customer information to employees requiring that information to provide products or services to you. We educate our employees about the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy, and data security.  
  
### How does Sterling Savings Bank collect my personal information?

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you   
\- open an account or deposit money  
\- pay your bills or apply for a loan  
\- use your credit or debit card  
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
### Why can't I limit all sharing?

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only  
\- sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness  
\- affiliates from using your information to market to you  
\- sharing for non-affiliates to market to you  
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
_**See below for more on your rights under state law.**_  
  
Definitions  
---  
  
### Affiliates

| Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  _Sterling Savings Bank does not share with our affiliates._  
  
### Non-affiliates

| Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.  _Sterling Savings Bank does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you._  
  
### Joint marketing

| A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.  _Our joint marketing partners include issuer of Sterling's credit card and credit life insurance provider._  
  
### Other important information

For California residents only: California law places additional limits on sharing information about California residents. In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about California residents with outside companies, except as permitted by law, such as with the consent of the customer or to service the customer's accounts.

For Sterling Savings Bank insurance product customers: Pursuant to certain state privacy laws, you may have the right to learn the substance of customer information collected about you and to learn whether the customer information has been disclosed to our affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties within the last two years. If you would like this information, please send your request in writing to: Sterling Savings Bank , 111 N. Wall St., Spokane, WA 99201. Sterling Savings Bank will provide such information if required by applicable law.

Sterling Savings Bank and Its Affiliates  
Affiliates of Sterling Savings Bank include Intervest-Mortgage Investment Company and Mason-McDuffie Financial Corporation.

Sterling Savings Bank is a Washington state-chartered bank that operates under the following trade names: Sterling and Argent Bank. Sterling Savings Bank does not operate under the STERLING brand in the State of California, but instead operates as "ARGENT BANK."
